A Guide to the Papers of the Dean of Students,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1953 July-1958 July (Box-folder 34:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1947 February-1953 February (Box-folder 34:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Sigma Phi Epsilon-November 1, 1947 Affair, 1947 November-1948 March (Box-folder 34:6)
- Fraternities, Social- Sigma Pi (Corinthian Club), 1957 March-1961 August (Box-folder 35:1)
- Fraternities, Social-St. Anthony Hall (Delta Psi), 1958 June-1961 August (Box-folder 35:2)
- Fraternities, Social-St. Anthony Hall (Delta Psi), 1951-1958 May (Box-folder 35:3)
- Fraternities, Social-St. Elmo Hall (Delta Phi), 1957 March-1961 August (Box-folder 35:4)
- Fraternities, Social-St. Elmo Hall (Delta Phi), 1946 May-1957 February (Box-folder 35:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Epsilon Phi (Tau Nu Club), 1956 March-1961 February (Box-folder 35:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Epsilon Phi (Tau Nu Club), 1955 December-1956 February (Box-folder 36:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1957 November-1961 August (Box-folder 36:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1955 November-1957 October (Box-folder 36:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Kappa Epsilon (Triangle Club), 1950 May-1955 October (Box-folder 36:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Tau Kappa Epsilon (Triangle Club), 1949 December-1950 March (Box-folder 36:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Chi, 1958 March-1961 August (Box-folder 36:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Chi, 1954 June-1958 February (Box-folder 36:7)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Chi, 1946 July-1954 May (Box-folder 37:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Delta Chi, 1956 December-1961 June (Box-folder 37:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Delta Chi, 1946 September-1956 November (Box-folder 37:3)
- Fraternities, Social-Theta Delta Chi, 1946 May-August (Box-folder 37:4)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Beta Tau, 1958 November-1961 August (Box-folder 37:5)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Beta Tau, 1953 February-1958 October (Box-folder 37:6)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Beta Tau, 1946 August-1952 November (Box-folder 37:7)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Psi, 1959 December-1961 June (Box-folder 38:1)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Psi, 1957 May-1959 November (Box-folder 38:2)
- Fraternities, Social-Zeta Psi, 1946 May-1957 April (Box-folder 38:3)
- Fraternities, Spicer Committee Report on, 1955 March (Box-folder 38:4)
- Frederick College, 1959 October-1960 May (Box-folder 38:5)
- Freshman Football-Housing, 1952 September (Box-folder 38:6)
- Geographical Clubs (Home Area), 1950 November-1954 October (Box-folder 38:7)
- George Peabody College, 1957 February (Box-folder 38:8)
- Glee Club, 1952 November-1957 April (Box-folder 38:9)
- Gooch Report on Intercollegiate Athletics, 1951 October-December (Box-folder 38:10)
- Grade Reports, 1951 March (Box-folder 38:11)
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1950 February-1955 July (Box-folder 38:12)
- Graduate School of Business Administration, 1954 November-1955 September, 1957 March (Box-folder 38:13)
- Graduating Class: Organization & Gifts, 1951 May-1956 November (Box-folder 39:1)
- Graduation Programs (Degrees Awarded), 1948 June-1952 June (Box-folder 39:2)
- Grounds Parking Permits, 1952 September-1955 (Box-folder 39:3)
- Guide Activities, 1951 October-1955 July (Box-folder 39:4)
- Gun Ring, 1953 June (Box-folder 39:5)
- Hamilton, Mrs. Sally- Landlord, 1951 January-December (Box-folder 39:6)
- Hazen Foundation, Committee on Student Counseling, 1951 April-1952 May (Box-folder 39:7)
- Hillel Foundation, 1956 May (Box-folder 39:8)
- Hinkle, Janet M.-Clerk-Stenographer, 1959 February-1960 April (Box-folder 39:9)
- History Club, 1953 January (Box-folder 39:10)
- History of the University, n.d. (Box-folder 39:11)
- Hollins College, 1954 March-1959 October (Box-folder 39:12)
- Honor Committee, 1960 June-1961 August (Box-folder 39:13)
- Honor Committee, 1958 June-1960 May (Box-folder 39:14)
- Honor Committee, 1954 September-1958 May (Box-folder 39:15)
- Honor Committee, 1952 February-1954 August (Box-folder 40:1)
- Honor Committee, 1950 January-1951 November (Box-folder 40:2)
- Honor Loan Fund, 1950 October-1954 February (Box-folder 40:3)
- Housing-General, 1960 January-1961 August (Box-folder 40:4)
- Housing-General, 1957 June-1959 December (Box-folder 40:5)
- Housing-General, 1955 October-1957 May (Box-folder 40:6)
- Housing-General, 1955 January-July (Box-folder 40:7)
- Housing-General, 1953 August-1954 December (Box-folder 40:8)
- Housing-General, 1952 September-1953 July (Box-folder 41:1)
- Housing-General, 1951 July-1952 August (Box-folder 41:2)
- Housing-General, 1949 October-1951 June (Box-folder 41:3)
- Housing-Assignments, Entering Class, 1960 May-1961 August (Box-folder 41:4)
- Housing-Copely Hill, 1950 November-1957 May (Box-folder 41:5)
- Housing-Damages, 1951 February, 1952 March-1953 June (Box-folder 41:6)
- Housing-Exceptions for First-Year Students A-L, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 41:7)
- Housing-Exceptions for First-Year Students M-Z, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 42:1)
- Housing-Floor Plans of McCormick Road Dorms, n. d. (Oversize 42)
- Housing-House Presidents, 1951 February (Box-folder 42:2)
- Housing-Humphreys House, 1951 January-1952 May (Box-folder 42:3)
- Housing-Lawn Applicants, 1952 February-1954 June (Box-folder 42:4)
- Housing-Lists & Room Changes, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 42:5)
- Housing Policies, 1951 February-1954 May (Box-folder 42:6)
- Housing-Second Year Living Arrangements, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 42:7)
- Illegal Cars, 1959 October, n.d. (Box-folder 42:8)
- IMP Society, 1952 January-1955 September (Box-folder 42:9)
- Indiana Technical College, 1956 January (Box-folder 42:10)
- Insurance Plans, 1953 January (Box-folder 42:11)
- Intermediate Honors, 1952 November, 1955 November (Box-folder 42:12)
- Intramural Sports Program, 1959 March-1960 June (Box-folder 42:13)
- Intramural Sports Program, 1950 August-1955 August (Box-folder 42:14)
- Jazz Society, 1954 April-1957 December (Box-folder 42:15)
- Jefferson Hall, 1952 November (Box-folder 42:16)
- Jefferson Sabres (Army ROTC), 1952 October-1954 November (Box-folder 42:17)
- Jefferson Society, 1950 December-1960 June (Box-folder 42:18)
- Joint Committee: Senior-Junior Colleges (American Association of Junior Colleges), 1958 August-1960 February (Box-folder 43:1)
- Judiciary Committee, 1959 October-1961 June (Box-folder 43:2)
- Judiciary Committee, 1954 December-1959 September (Box-folder 43:3)
- Junior College Plan, 1959 November-1960 December (Box-folder 43:4)
- Kansas, University of, 1953 January (Box-folder 43:5)
- Key Ring, 1953 June-July (Box-folder 43:6)
- Landladies, 1946 November-1952 May (Box-folder 43:7)
- Law, School of, 1950 December-1956 October (Box-folder 43:8)
- Lehigh University, 1953 December (Box-folder 43:9)
- Liberal Arts Committee, 1947 June-1954 January (Box-folder 43:10)
- Longwood College, 1959 October-December (Box-folder 43:11)
- Lower Division, 1951 February-1953 August (Box-folder 43:12)
- Lower Division, 1949 October-1951 January (Box-folder 44:1)
- Lower Division, n.d. (Box-folder 44:2)
- Lower Division-Appraisals of Entering Students, 1952 December-1953 January (Box-folder 44:3)
- Lower Division, Committee on the, 1953 September-1957 February (Box-folder 44:4)
- Lower Division, Committee on the, 1952 June-1953 August (Box-folder 44:5)
- Lower Division, Committee on the, 1950 May-1952 May (Box-folder 44:6)
- Lower Division, Housing Sub-Committee, 1951 July-1952 March (Box-folder 44:7)
- Lower Division-Special Program, 1953 September (Box-folder 44:8)
- Madison College, 1950 November-1960 June (Box-folder 44:9)
- Mail Box Theft Case, 1951 February-June (Box-folder 44:10)
- Mary Baldwin College, 1952 September-1958 October (Box-folder 44:11)
- Mary Washington College, 1950 September-1960 February (Box-folder 44:12)
- Maryland, University of, 1955 December (Box-folder 44:13)
- Maury Hall, 1951 November (Box-folder 45:1)
- McIntire School of Commerce, 1952 December-1956 December (Box-folder 45:2)
- Medical College of Virginia, 1954 May-1956 January (Box-folder 45:3)
- Medicine, School of, 1950 March-1955 October (Box-folder 45:4)
- Miami, University of, 1955 August-1956 January (Box-folder 45:5)
- Mickey, Elinor L.-Clerk-Stenographer, 1954 January-June (Box-folder 45:6)
- Mid-Winters Dance Weekend Car Registration, 1960 February-April (Box-folder 45:7)
- Mike Roberts Color Photos, 1951 February-1952 June (Box-folder 45:8)
- Military Affairs, 1952 June-1955 October (Box-folder 45:9)
- Military Affairs, 1950 October-1952 May (Box-folder 45:10)
- Military Program at the University, 1960 May-1961 August (Box-folder 45:11)
- Military-Selective Service, 1956 March-1960 June (Box-folder 45:12)
- Military-Selective Service, 1955 June-1956 February, n.d. (Box-folder 45:13)
- Minnesota, University of, 1953 March-1954 July (Box-folder 46:1)
- Missouri, University of, 1953 March-1955 January (Box-folder 46:2)
- Monroe Rifles, 1952 October (Box-folder 46:3)
- Motor Vehicle Rules & Regulations, 1959 February-1961 April (Box-folder 46:4)
- Motor Vehicle Rules & Regulations, 1950 September-1958 November (Box-folder 46:5)
- Music, Department of, 1953 April-1956 March (Box-folder 46:6)
- National Council of Independent Schools, 1950 April-May (Box-folder 46:7)
- National Jazz Fraternity, 1957 May-1960 April (Box-folder 46:8)
- National Student Association, 1953 May-1955 June (Box-folder 46:9)
- Naval Reserve Officers' Training Corps, 1949 July-1952 May (Box-folder 46:10)
- New Buildings Committee, 1947 August, 1954 October, n.d. (Box-folder 46:11)
- Newcomb Hall, 1959 August-1960 June (Box-folder 46:12)
- Newcomb Hall Additions and Alterations, 1961 August-1965 August (Box-folder 46:13)
- Newcomb Hall Bookstore, 1964 November-1965 July (Box-folder 46:14)
- Newcomb Hall (Student Union Building Planning), 1947 August-1949 August (Box-folder 47:1)
- Newman Hall, 1952 December-1957 June (Box-folder 47:2)
- News Service, 1951 March-1955 August (Box-folder 47:3)
- Norfolk Division-College of William & Mary-Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1952 November (Box-folder 47:4)
- Nursing, School of, 1949 February-1960 November (Box-folder 47:5)
- Office Personnel, 1950 February-1958 December (Box-folder 47:6)
- Open House: Engineering Science, 1950 March-1954 May (Box-folder 47:7)
- Orientation Program, 1960 October-1961 September (Box-folder 47:8)
- Orientation Program, 1959 September-1950 September (Box-folder 47:9)
- Orientation Program, 1955 July-1959 August (Box-folder 47:10)
- Orientation Program, 1954 May-1955 June (Box-folder 48:1)
- Orientation Program, 1952 September-1953 September (Box-folder 48:2)
- Orientation Program, 1948 December-1952 August (Box-folder 48:3)
- Outing Club, 1953 September-1960 June (Box-folder 48:4)
- Page House, 1951 February-1953 March (Box-folder 48:5)
- Party Registrations (Non-Fraternity), 1957 September-1960 May (Box-folder 48:6)
- Patrick Henry Literary Society, 1952 March (Box-folder 48:7)
- Pennsylvania State University, 1950-1957 May (Box-folder 48:8)
- Personnel Office, 1952 August-1961 August (Box-folder 48:9)
- Personnel Office, 1950 January-1952 July (Box-folder 49:1)
- Philadelphia Trip, 1959 November (Box-folder 49:2)
- Phi Sigma Award, 1960 February-April (Box-folder 49:3)
- Physical Education, Department of, 1952 September-1954 November (Box-folder 49:4)
- Physical Examinations-Graduate & Professional School Students, 1960 May (Box-folder 49:5)
- Pittsburgh, University of, 1957 January (Box-folder 49:6)
- Place of Meeting Committee, Virginia Academy of Science, 1957 April-1958 April (Box-folder 49:7)
- Placement-Student Affairs Office, 1949 December-1955 July (Box-folder 49:8)
- Police-City, County, University, 1953 February-1961 August (Box-folder 49:9)
- Police-City, County, University, 1950 November-1953 January (Box-folder 49:10)
- Police Reports-University, 1961 March-September (Box-folder 49:11)
- Police Reports-University, 1960 August-1961 February (Box-folder 50:1)
- Police Reports-University, 1959 August-1960 July (Box-folder 50:2)
- Police Reports-University, 1958 June-1959 July (Box-folder 50:3)
- Police Reports-University, 1957 April-1958 May (Box-folder 50:4)
- Police Reports-University, 1955 February-1957 March (Box-folder 50:5)
- Police Reports-University, 1953 June-1955 January (Box-folder 50:6)
- Police Reports-University, 1952 October-1953 May (Box-folder 51:1)
- Police Reports-University, 1951 September-1952 September (Box-folder 51:2)
- Polo Club, 1954 April-1960 January (Box-folder 51:3)
- Pre-Medical Evaluation Committee, 1953 September-1961 August (Box-folder 51:4)
- President-Darden, Colgate W., 1952 October-1959 July (Box-folder 51:5)
- President-Darden, Colgate W., 1949 September-1952 September (Box-folder 51:6)
- President-Shannon, Edgar F., 1959 March-1961 July (Box-folder 51:7)
- President's Committee on Session Length and Scholarships, 1957 September-October (Box-folder 51:8)
- Princeton University, 1951 April-1956 April (Box-folder 51:9)
- Programs of Study of Entering College Students, 1952 December-1953 January (Box-folder 52:1)
- Provost, 1956 October-1960 June (Box-folder 52:2)
- Publications-Plans & Pieces, 1950 November-1951 July (Box-folder 52:3)
- Public Occasions, Committee on, 1948 October-1956 June (Box-folder 52:4)
- Public Relations Committee, 1959 March-1960 September (Box-folder 52:5)
- Public Relations Sub-Committee: To Review & Appraise General Publications & News Services, 1959 April-1960 March (Box-folder 52:6)
- Punch & Julep Club, 1957 December-1960 May (Box-folder 52:7)
- Purchasing Department, 1952 November-1957 January (Box-folder 52:8)
- Purdue University, 1952 December-1957 March (Box-folder 52:9)
- Queens Club, 1951 February-1953 May (Box-folder 52:10)
- Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1952 January-1959 December (Box-folder 52:11)
- Raven Award Committee, 1958-1961 April (Box-folder 52:12)
- Raven Society, 1950 April-1961 June (Box-folder 52:13)
- Reading Clinic, 1952 March-September (Box-folder 53:1)
- Re-Admissions, 1951 June-1953 May (Box-folder 53:2)
- Red Cross Drive, 1958, 1960, 1961 (Box-folder 53:3)
- Registrar, 1960 June-1961 July (Box-folder 53:4)
- Registrar, 1959 April-1960 May (Box-folder 53:5)
- Registrar, 1954 March-1959 March (Box-folder 53:6)
- Registrar, 1948-1953 December (Box-folder 53:7)
- Registration Forms & Procedures, 1948 August-1954 June (Box-folder 53:8)
- Religion at the University, 1960 September (Box-folder 53:9)
- Residence House Guide, 1952-1953 April (Box-folder 53:10)
- Resident Faculty Advisers, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 54:1)
- Richmond, University of, 1957 March (Box-folder 54:2)
- Robberies, 1952 November-1953 July (Box-folder 54:3)
- Rockefeller Foundation Scholarships, 1955 January (Box-folder 54:4)
- Rules & Courses, Committee on, 1952 February-1954 February (Box-folder 54:5)
- Sailing Club, 1955 February, 1956 February (Box-folder 54:6)
- Scarab, 1952 October (Box-folder 54:7)
- Scholarships, 1946 August-1952 May (Box-folder 54:8)
- Scholarships: Acceptances, Rejections, 1952 June-1954 March (Box-folder 54:9)
- Scholarships Awards, 1951-1952 September (Box-folder 54:10)
- Scholarship Committee, 1961 February-August (Box-folder 54:11)
- Scholarship Committee, 1960 August-1961 January (Box-folder 54:12)
- Scholarships Awards, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 55:1)
- Scholarships Awards, 1958 February-1959 April (Box-folder 55:2)
- Scholarships Awards, 1957 [July]-December (Box-folder 55:3)
- Scholarships Awards, 1955 June-1957 March (Box-folder 55:4)
- Scholarships Awards, 1954 [October]-1955 May (Box-folder 55:5)
- Scholarships Awards, [1953]-1954 September (Box-folder 55:6)
- Students Club, International, n.d. (Box-folder 55:7)
- Scholarship Committee, 1960 January-July (Box-folder 56:1)
- Scholarship Committee, 1958 February-1959 December (Box-folder 56:2)
- Scholarship Committee, 1955 July-1958 January (Box-folder 56:3)
- Scholarships-Grants-in-Aid, 1953 January-1955 April (Box-folder 56:4)
- Scholarships, Loans & Employment, Committee on, 1954 September-1958 March (Box-folder 56:5)
- Scholarships, Loans & Employment, Committee on, 1954 February-August (Box-folder 56:6)
- Scholarships, Loans & Employment, Committee on, 1953 May-1954 January (Box-folder 56:7)
- Scholarships, Loans & Employment, Committee on, 1952 June-1953 April (Box-folder 57:4)
- Scholarships, Loans & Employment, Committee on, 1952 January-May (Box-folder 57:5)
- Seven Society, 1959 April-1960 April (Box-folder 57:6)
- "Sit-Ins" at the University, 1961 March (Box-folder 57:7)
- Skull & Keys, 1956 April, 1957 April (Box-folder 57:8)
- Social Events at Women's Colleges, 1960 December-1961 May (Box-folder 57:9)
- Solicitation on University Property, 1951 August-1955 October (Box-folder 57:10)
- Sororities, 1950-1956 May (Box-folder 57:11)
- Southeastern Regional Deans of Men, 1954 January-1956 January (Box-folder 57:12)
- Southern Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, 1954 September-October (Box-folder 57:13)
- Spanish Club, 1959 December (Box-folder 57:14)
- Spectator, The, 1951 March-1959 May (Box-folder 57:15)
- Speech & Drama, Department of, 1950 March-1955 April (Box-folder 57:16)
- Stadium Committee, 1952 October-1953 October (Box-folder 57:17)
- Stagg, Miss Sarah, 1959 October-December (Box-folder 57:18)
- Statistics & Studies-Miscellaneous, 1950 October-1956 February (Box-folder 58:1)
- Student Activities Committee, 1960 June-1961 June (Box-folder 58:2)
- Student Activities Committee, 1959 July-1960 May (Box-folder 58:3)
- Student Activities Committee, 1959 May-June (Box-folder 58:4)
- Student Activities Committee, 1958 May-1959 April (Box-folder 58:5)
- Student Activities Committee, 1957 May-1958 April (Box-folder 58:6)
- Student Activities Committee, 1954 May-1957 April (Box-folder 59:1)
- Student Activities Committee-The Cavalier Daily, 1960 February-1961 June (Box-folder 59:2)
- Student Activities Committee-The Cavalier Daily, 1959 March-1960 January (Box-folder 59:3)
- Student Activities Committee-The Cavalier Daily, 1957 September-1959 February (Box-folder 59:4)
- Student Activities Committee-The Cavalier Daily, 1952 February-1957 August (Box-folder 59:5)
- Student Affairs Assistant, 1951 October-1952 April (Box-folder 59:6)
- Student Affairs, Director of, 1954 September-1956 January (Box-folder 59:7)
- Student Affairs, Director of, 1952 September-1954 August (Box-folder 60:1)
- Student Affairs, Director of, 1950 June-1951 May (Box-folder 60:2)
- Student Affairs, Director of-Counseling & Discipline, 1953 September-1955 June (Box-folder 60:3)
- Student Attitudes & Opinions, 1949 February, 1951 April, n.d. (Box-folder 60:4)
- Student Collections, 1953 June-1954 July (Box-folder 60:5)
- Student Council, 1960 July-1961 July (Box-folder 60:6)
- Student Council, 1959 December-1960 June (Box-folder 60:7)
- Student Council, 1958 December-1959 November (Box-folder 61:1)
- Student Council, 1957 July-1958 November (Box-folder 61:2)
- Student Council, 1956 September-1957 May (Box-folder 61:3)
- Student Council, 1955 June-1956 August (Box-folder 61:4)
- Student Council, 1954 August-1955 May (Box-folder 61:5)
- Student Council, 1954 January-May (Box-folder 61:6)
- Student Council, 1952 December-1953 December (Box-folder 62:1)
- Student Council, 1951 March-1952 November (Box-folder 62:2)
- Student Council, 1950 October-1951 February (Box-folder 62:3)
- Student Council, 1949 January-1950 September (Box-folder 62:4)
- Student Council, 1946 February-1948 December (Box-folder 62:5)
- Student Council Cases, 1955 August-1956 June (Box-folder 62:6)
- Student Council Traffic Survey & Recommendations, 1955 April, September (Box-folder 62:7)
- Student Directory, 1953 August-1955 October (Box-folder 62:8)
- Student Government in the Houses, 1951 March-April (Box-folder 63:1)
- Student Government Leaders Meetings, 1959 September-1960 May (Box-folder 63:2)
- Student Health: General, 1960 (Box-folder 63:3)
- Student Health: General, 1959 March-November (Box-folder 63:4)
- Student Health: General, 1958 January-1959 February (Box-folder 63:5)
- Student Health: General, 1951-1957 November (Box-folder 63:6)
- Student Health Service: General Correspondence, 1952 November-1961 July (Box-folder 63:7)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1960 January-1961 May (Box-folder 63:8)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1959 May-December (Box-folder 63:9)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1959 January-April (Box-folder 63:10)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1958 May-December (Box-folder 63:11)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1958 January-April (Box-folder 63:12)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1957 (Box-folder 63:13)
- Student Health Service: Hospital Reports, 1953 October-1956 December (Box-folder 64:1)
- Student Health Service: Sanitation Reports, 1959 August-1961 July (Box-folder 64:2)
- Student Health Service: Sanitation Reports, 1957 January-1959 August (Box-folder 64:3)
- Student Health Service: Sanitation Reports, 1955 January-1956 December (Box-folder 64:4)
- Student Health Service: Sanitation Reports, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 64:5)
- Student Health Service: Sanitation Reports, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 64:6)
- "Students for America," 1953 November-1954 April (Box-folder 64:7)
- Student Identification Photographs, 1951 (Box-folder 64:8)
- Student Legal Forms, 1950 December-1951 May (Box-folder 64:9)
- Student Riots, 1959 (Box-folder 64:10)
- Student Riots, 1958 (Box-folder 64:11)
- Student Union (University Union), 1967 (Box-folder 64:12)
- Student Union (University Union), 1966 June-December (Box-folder 64:13)
- Student Union (University Union), 1966 January-May (Box-folder 65:1)
- Student Union (University Union), 1965 June-December (Box-folder 65:2)
- Student Union (University Union), 1965 January-May (Box-folder 65:3)
- Student Union (University Union), 1964 (Box-folder 65:4)
- Student Union (University Union), 1963 (Box-folder 65:5)
- Student Union (University Union), 1961 (Box-folder 65:6)
- Student Union (University Union), 1959 October-1960 December (Box-folder 65:7)
- Student Union (University Union), 1957 October-1959 May (Box-folder 65:8)
- Student Union (University Union), 1957 May-September (Box-folder 65:9)
- Student Union (University Union), 1955 June-1957 April (Box-folder 66:1)
- Student Union (University Union), 1954 July-1955 May (Box-folder 66:2)
- Student Union (University Union), 1954 January-June (Box-folder 66:3)
- Student Union (University Union), 1952 August-1953 December (Box-folder 66:4)
- Student Union (University Union), 1950 October-1952 February (Box-folder 66:5)
- Study of Women Visitors in Men's Dormitories, 1960 May-October (Box-folder 66:6)
- Summer Session: General, 1961 (Box-folder 66:7)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1961 (Box-folder 66:8)
- Summer Session: General, 1959 November-1960 November (Box-folder 66:9)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1960 March-June 22 (Box-folder 66:10)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1960 June 23-September (Box-folder 66:11)
- Summer Session: General, 1959 (Box-folder 67:1)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1959 (Box-folder 67:2)
- Summer Session: General, 1958 (Box-folder 67:3)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1958 (Box-folder 67:4)
- Summer Session: General, 1957 (Box-folder 67:5)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1957 (Box-folder 67:6)
- Summer Session: General, 1955 October-1956 September (Box-folder 67:7)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1956 (Box-folder 67:8)
- Summer Session: General, 1955 (Box-folder 67:9)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1955 (Box-folder 67:10)
- Summer Session: General, 1953 December-1954 September (Box-folder 67:11)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1954 (Box-folder 67:12)
- Summer Session: General, 1953 (Box-folder 68:1)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1953 (Box-folder 68:2)
- Summer Session: General, 1952 (Box-folder 68:3)
- Summer Session: Fraternities, 1952 (Box-folder 68:4)
- Summer Session: General, 1951 (Box-folder 68:5)